Anyone who identifies as a woman
understands it's a journey.
Right? Being a woman
is a journey.
Lots of twists and turns.
We dealing with things
that people don't even...
know that we're dealing with.
-Titties.
-(AUDIENCE CHUCKLES)
Okay?
It don't matter what size
yo titties is...
At the end of the day,
when you take your bra off,
they audibly sigh.
-(SIGHS)
-(AUDIENCE LAUGHS)
You going back to the motherland
in your living room.
(SINGS)
Let 'em hang. Let 'em swing.
'Kay, there's a crowd outside,
chanting,
"Free the titties!
Free the titties!"
There's a reporter in your room
interviewing your nipples,
like, "How's it feel to be free
from that padded cell?"
"My God, I feel so good,
I feel the wind in my hair."
"There's hair on nipples?"
"Yeah."
(LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE)
Then we have these periods...
-(CHUCKLING)
-Right.
I thought by now
I'd be used to it.
I really did, but still
it be like, "Ta-da."
I'm like,
"Where did you come from?"
(LAUGHTER)
And so I find myself,
more often than I'd like to,
in a public restroom
doing this.
Wrapping toilet paper
around a crotch.
(LAUGHTER)
Becuase by 37, I've become
a menstrual MacGyver.
(LAUGHTER)